<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Python on Siddhanth J Ajri</title>
    <link>https://SiddAjriY2Jaccount.github.io/techs/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Python on Siddhanth J Ajri</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Siddhanth J Ajri</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 19:47:09 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://SiddAjriY2Jaccount.github.io/techs/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Intern</title>
      <link>https://SiddAjriY2Jaccount.github.io/portfolio/wipro_internship/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://SiddAjriY2Jaccount.github.io/portfolio/wipro_internship/</guid>
      <description>I was fortunate to have the opportunity to work at one of the biggest IT firms in India today, Wipro Ltd., early in my career. As an intern in the Edge Analytics division, I was first tasked with acclimatising myself to the various cloud and edge infrastructures that I would come across. Post that, I was introduced to Docker and DevOps culture, as my primary task for the next month would be to dockerize Python-based applications that were ready to be deployed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Science Intern</title>
      <link>https://SiddAjriY2Jaccount.github.io/portfolio/innointel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://SiddAjriY2Jaccount.github.io/portfolio/innointel/</guid>
      <description>In what was my first internship experience, I worked at Innointel Global as a Data Science Intern. I was tasked with developing a relevance classification pipeline for the IESM project. Multiple datasets of websites and their summaries were compiled and the website needed to be classified as relevant to a domain mentioned such as &amp;lsquo;Science &amp;amp; Technology&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;Manufacturing&amp;rsquo; etc. The pipeline and model developed as part of the internship was directly responsible for pushing deliverables of relevance classification for 42k data points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KRIDA - Diagnosis of Intellectual Disability</title>
      <link>https://SiddAjriY2Jaccount.github.io/portfolio/krida/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://SiddAjriY2Jaccount.github.io/portfolio/krida/</guid>
      <description>This is the flagship product of our entrepreneurial venture, Vincere Solutions. This desktop application developed using Python incorporates a set of standardized tests, the results of which are fed as input to a Deep Neural Network Model, to detect the early onset of Intellectual Disability (ID). The app was reviewed in a conference conducted by Victoria Hospital and received certification. Furthermore, talks to implement the app in primary schools as a screening tool for ID are in progress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>StreamItV2</title>
      <link>https://SiddAjriY2Jaccount.github.io/portfolio/streamit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://SiddAjriY2Jaccount.github.io/portfolio/streamit/</guid>
      <description>A web application that streams multimedia, both audio and video, which can be accessed by all registered users of the app. Users are able to modify media uploaded by them, but are not authorised to modify media uploaded by other users. Users with admin rights are able to freely add or delete media from the app. Users are also provided the functionality to upload and delete comments.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>